# Piotr Dziubek

#### **DETAILS**

Bielany, ul Nad Sołą 9, 32-651 Nowa Wieś 723 516 349 dziubekp2@gmail.com

### **ABOUT ME**

I am computer science engineer with 5 years of programming experience. For the past three years I have been largely involved in C# programing. For two months I started working with Xamarin. After work, I try to learn some new technologies - including JS and JS libraries, frameworks.

# PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C# .NET, Core JavaScript React MSSQL HTML, CSS

# **LANGUAGES**

- ENGLISH- level B1/B2
- DEUTCH- level B1

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, AILLERON

(October 2019 - Now, Bielsko-Biała)

 Working with .net core and .net apps based on WPF enhanced by DevExpress Framework - Creating reports based on xTraReports, working with databases (EF Core, PostgreSQL)

#### PROGRAMMER, BST CDN PARTNER

(January 2016 - October 2019, Bielsko-Biała)

- Implementation of solutions for Enova ERP system based on C# language.
- Working with WebService, REST. Programing mobile devices (Windows CE and Xamarin)
- Contact with customer collecting requirements and data to create a better solution
- Refactoring and changes in online stores based on Yii framework (PHP).

#### **INTERN-PROGRAMMER, TRW**

(June-December 2015, Czechowice-Dziedzice)

- Working with web applications (Javascript, .NET, HTML, CSS)
- Creating a mobile application for Android phones for monitoring production based on API
- Creating code documentation and testing applications

#### **SELLER, PC MEDIA**

(January-February 2013r., Kety)

 Sale of computers, computer components, photocopying, document lamination

# **EDUCATION**

#### **IT ENGINEER**

AGH University of Science and Technology (2012-2016)

 Studies in applied computer science ended up with a good degree.

# **HOBBIES**

- Basketball
- New technologies
- Playing on musical instruments
- Running

# **SKILLS**

- SVN System, GIT,
- JIRA
- Project patterns
- Knowledge of computer architecture
- Car driving license
- Carrying out implementations

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)".